

# YOVIE ALFAGUISTUTA

## Web Developer

## **ABOUT ME**

I am 23 years old and I am a web developer graduated in 2021. Coding on React JS, Laravel and Go Language with 2+ years experience. Serving 30+ users to build complex web application. My greatest strength is problem solving and logical thinking. I am very interested to use or learn the latest technology

#### **SOFT SKILL**

- Problem Solving
- Logical Thinking
- Creativty
- Time Management
- Teamwork

## **TECH STACK**

- React JS
- Go
- Laravel
- **i**Query









## **PROGRAMMING TOOLS**

- Git
  - Jest Github & Gitlab
- Docker & PM2
- Go Fiber
- Sentry
- Linux
- Pgsql & Mysql
- CI / CD (Jenkins)
- Postman & Swagger

## **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021 Bachelor degree S1 Informatika (S.Kom)

at Universitas Teknokrat Indonesia.

GPA 3,45.

2015 - 2017 High school graduate from SMAN

5 Bandar Lampung, Science Major

### **EXPERIENCE**

Web Developer Microdata Indonesia

2020 - 2022

Create, debug, test, analytze and modify more than 20+ complex apps from start to production

Web Developer Freelance 2020 - 2022

Develop more than 10+ variant applica-

tion and system for thesis

Internship **Android Developer** BAPPEDA (Intern) 2020

Developing 2 Android Mobile Apps for Government activities within 2 months of

work

### **LANGUAGE**

Indonesia

English







#### **Email**

yoviealfaguistuta@gmail.com



My Site

http://yoviealfaguistuta.site



#### Address

Pulau Sanama Street, Bandar Lampung

